Guide to the Merton Stoltz Files 1959-1978
Brown University Library
- Files: 1976-1977, 1975-1977; Series 14
  - General, Series 14. Subseries A
    - Swearer, H.R., President, 1977 (Box 72, Folder XIV.64)
    - Title IX, 1975-1976 (Box 72, Folder XIV.65)
    - Tougaloo College, 1976-1977 (Box 72, Folder XIV.66)
    - Transitional Summer Program - Report & Review, 1976-1977 (Box 72, Folder XIV.67)
    - Undergraduate Council of Students, 1976-1977 (Box 72, Folder XIV.68)
    - United Way Campaign, 1976-1977 (Box 72, Folder XIV.69)
    - WBRU, 1976-1977 (Box 72, Folder XIV.70)
    - Wolk, Ronald - VP University Relations, 1976-1977 (Box 72, Folder XIV.71)
    - Women's Groups - Correspondence, 1976-1977 (Box 72, Folder XIV.72)
  - Academic Departments, Series 14. Subseries B
    - Afro-American Studies Program, 1976-1977 (Box 73, Folder XIV.73)
    - American Civilization Program, 1976-1977 (Box 73, Folder XIV.74)
    - Anthropology, 1976-1977 (Box 73, Folder XIV.75)
    - Applied Mathematics, 1976-1977 (Box 73, Folder XIV.76)
    - Art, 1976-1977 (Box 73, Folder XIV.77)
    - Athletics, 1976-1977 (Box 73, Folder XIV.78)
    - Bio-Med Sciences, 1976-1977 (Box 73, Folder XIV.79)
    - Chemistry, 1976-1977 (Box 73, Folder XIV.80)
    - Classics, 1976-1977 (Box 73, Folder XIV.81)
    - Comparative Literature (Box 73, Folder XIV.82)
    - Computer Science Program, 1976-1977 (Box 73, Folder XIV.83)
    - Economics, 1976-1977 (Box 73, Folder XIV.84)
    - Education, 1976-1977 (Box 73, Folder XIV.85)
    - Egyptology, 1976-1977 (Box 73, Folder XIV.86)
    - Engineering, 1976-1977 (Box 73, Folder XIV.87)
    - English, 1976-1977 (Box 73, Folder XIV.88)
    - French Studies, 1976-1977 (Box 73, Folder XIV.89)
    - Geological Sciences, 1976-1977 (Box 74, Folder XIV.90)
    - German, 1976-1977 (Box 74, Folder XIV.91)
    - Hispanic & Italian Studies, 1976-1977 (Box 74, Folder XIV.92)
    - History, 1976-1977 (Box 74, Folder XIV.93)
    - History of Mathematics, 1976-1977 (Box 74, Folder XIV.94)
    - Library - Rockefeller, 1976-1977 (Box 74, Folder XIV.95)
    - Churchwell Eval. Material, 1976-1977 (Box 74, Folder XIV.96)
    - Library - John Carter Brown, 1976-1977 (Box 74, Folder XIV.97)
    - Library - John Hay, 1976-1977 (Box 74, Folder XIV.98)
    - Library - Annmary Brown Memorial, 1976-1977 (Box 74, Folder XIV.99)
    - Mathematics, 1976-1977 (Box 74, Folder XIV.100)
    - Music, 1976-1977 (Box 74, Folder XIV.101)
    - Philosophy, 1976-1977 (Box 74, Folder XIV.102)
    - Physics, 1976-1977 (Box 74, Folder XIV.103)
    - Political Science, 1976-1977 (Box 74, Folder XIV.104)
    - Psychology, 1976-1977 (Box 74, Folder XIV.105)
    - Religious Studies, 1976-1977 (Box 74, Folder XIV.106)
    - Renaissance Studies, 1976-1977 (Box 74, Folder XIV.107)
    - Slavic Languages, 1976-1977 (Box 74, Folder XIV.108)
    - Sociology, 1976-1977 (Box 74, Folder XIV.109)
- Files: 1977-1978, 1975-1978; Series 15
  - General, Series 15. Subseries A
    - Provost's Account, 1977-1978 (Box 75, Folder XV.1)
    - Litigation Account, 1977-1978 (Box 75, Folder XV.2)
    - Miscellaneous Accounts, 1977-1978 (Box 75, Folder XV.3)
    - Admission Office, 1977-1978 (Box 75, Folder XV.4)
    - Alumni/Development Office, 1977-1978 (Box 75, Folder XV.5)
    - Brown University Press, 1977-1978 (Box 75, Folder XV.6)
    - Brown University Press - Funding for Backus Diary, 1977-1978 (Box 75, Folder XV.7)
    - Chaplain's Office, 1977-1978 (Box 76, Folder XV.8)
    - Foreign Student & Faculty Office, 1977-1978 (Box 76, Folder XV.9)
    - Commencement, 1977-1978 (Box 76, Folder XV.10)
    - Consortium on Financing Higher Education (COFHE), 1977-1978 (Box 76, Folder XV.11)
    - Controller's Office, 1977-1978 (Box 76, Folder XV.12)
    - Copyright Information, 1977-1978 (Box 76, Folder XV.13)
    - Correspondence, 1977-1978 (Box 76, Folder XV.14)
    - Dean of the College, 1977-1978 (Box 76, Folder XV.15)
    - Dean of the Faculty & Academic Affairs, 1977-1978 (Box 76, Folder XV.16)
    - Dean of the Graduate School, 1977-1978 (Box 76, Folder XV.17)
    - EPE Reports, 1977-1978 (Box 76, Folder XV.18)
    - Equal Opportunity Office, 1977-1978 (Box 76, Folder XV.19)
    - Financial Aid Office, 1977-1978 (Box 76, Folder XV.20)
    - Student Employment Office, 1977-1978 (Box 76, Folder XV.21)
    - HEW-General, 1977-1978 (Box 76, Folder XV.22)
    - HEW - Handicapped, 1977-1978 (Box 76, Folder XV.23)
    - HEW - Title LX, 1977-1978 (Box 76, Folder XV.24)
    - Honorary Degrees - Suggestions for…, 1977-1978 (Box 77, Folder XV.25)
    - Institutional Research, 1977-1978 (Box 77, Folder XV.26)
    - Ladd, 1978 (Box 77, Folder XV.27)
    - Paul F. Maeder, 1977-1978 (Box 77, Folder XV.28)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence - Campus, 1977-1978 (Box 77, Folder XV.29)
    - Off-Campus, 1977-1978 (Box 77, Folder XV.30)
    - Kelsey Murdoch, 1977-1978 (Box 77, Folder XV.31)
    - NEASC - Accreditation Visit, 1977-1978 (Box 78, Folder XV.32)
    - NEASC - Accreditation Visit, 1975 (Box 78, Folder XV.33)
    - Personnel & Budget, 1977-1978 (Box 78, Folder XV.34)
    - Change Forms (Box 78, Folder XV.35)
    - Office of Personnel and Budget - Time Sheets, 1977-1978 (Box 78, Folder XV.36)
    - Office of Personnel and Budget - Records, 1977-1978 (Box 78, Folder XV.37)
    - Provost's Office, 1977-1978 (Box 78, Folder XV.38)
    - Purchasing, 1977-1978 (Box 78, Folder XV.39)
    - Richard Ramsden, 1977-1978 (Box 78, Folder XV.40)
    - Research Services (Bert Hil), 1977-1978 (Box 78, Folder XV.41)
    - Requests for Publications, 1977-1978 (Box 78, Folder XV.42)
    - RI Education Council & Commisioner of Education, 1977-1978 (Box 78, Folder XV.43)
    - Howard R. Swearer, 1977-1978 (Box 78, Folder XV.44)
    - Transitional Summer Program, 1977-1978 (Box 78, Folder XV.45)
    - Tuition Benefits, 1977-1978 (Box 78, Folder XV.46)
    - Ronald Wolk, 1977-1978 (Box 78, Folder XV.47)
    - Merton P. Stoltz - Personal, 1977-1978 (Box 79, Folder XV.48)
  - Academic Departments, Series 15. Subseries B
    - Anthropology, 1977-1978 (Box 79, Folder XV.49)
    - Applied Mathematics, 1977-1978 (Box 79, Folder XV.50)
    - Athletics, 1977-1978 (Box 79, Folder XV.51)
    - Bio-Med Commonwealth Fund, 1977-1978 (Box 79, Folder XV.52)
    - Bio-Med Sciences Council, 1977-1978 (Box 79, Folder XV.53)
    - Bio- Med Sciences, 1977-1978 (Box 79, Folder XV.54)
    - Chemistry, 1977-1978 (Box 79, Folder XV.55)
    - Computer Lab, 1977-1978 (Box 79, Folder XV.56)
    - Economics, 1977-1978 (Box 79, Folder XV.57)
    - Education, 1977-1978 (Box 79, Folder XV.58)
    - Egyptology, 1977-1978 (Box 79, Folder XV.59)
    - Engineering, 1977-1978 (Box 79, Folder XV.60)
    - English, 1977-1978 (Box 79, Folder XV.61)
    - French Studies, 1977-1978 (Box 79, Folder XV.62)
    - Hispanic & Italian Studies, 1977-1978 (Box 79, Folder XV.63)
    - Library - Annmary Brown Memorial, 1977-1978 (Box 79, Folder XV.64)
    - John Carter Brown, 1977-1978 (Box 79, Folder XV.65)
    - John Hay, 1977-1978 (Box 79, Folder XV.66)
    - Rockefeller, 1977-1978 (Box 79, Folder XV.67)
    - Mathematics, 1977-1978 (Box 79, Folder XV.68)
    - Physics, 1977-1978 (Box 79, Folder XV.69)
    - Political Science, 1977-1978 (Box 79, Folder XV.70)
    - Psychology, 1977-1978 (Box 79, Folder XV.71)
    - Religious Studies, 1977-1978 (Box 79, Folder XV.72)
    - Slavic Languages, 1977-1978 (Box 79, Folder XV.73)
- Historical Files, 1968-1973; Series 16
  - Planning Committee, 1972 (Box 80, Folder XVI.1)
  - Presurvey Material - Bio- Med, 1972 (Box 80, Folder XVI.2)
  - Budget- Request Forms, 1972-1973 (Box 80, Folder XVI.3)
  - Black Student Enrollment Situation, 1968 (Box 80, Folder XVI.4)
- Committees, 1973-1978; Series 17
  - Appointments & Promotions, 1974-1975 (Box 81, Folder XVII.1)
  - Academic Policy, 1974-1975 (Box 81, Folder XVII.2)
  - Calender Committee, 1974-1975 (Box 81, Folder XVII.3)
  - Informal Committee on World Problems, 1974-1976 (Box 81, Folder XVII.4)
  - Academic Policy, 1975-1976 (Box 81, Folder XVII.5)
  - Administrative Committee on Appointments & Promotions, 1975-1976 (Box 82, Folder XVII.6)
  - ACUP, 1975-1976 (Box 82, Folder XVII.7)
  - Human Subject Committee, 1974-1976 (Box 82, Folder XVII.8)
  - Masters of Social Thought Program Committee, 1975-1977 (Box 82, Folder XVII.9)
  - N.E. Radio Observatory Committee- NEROC, 1975-1977 (Box 82, Folder XVII.10)
  - Program & Research Development, 1975-1976 (Box 82, Folder XVII.11)
  - Advisory Committee on University Planning, 1975-1976 (Box 83, Folder XVII.12)
  - Committee on YRO - Calender, 1974-1976 (Box 83, Folder XVII.13)
  - Committee on Calender, 1973-1974 (Box 84, Folder XVII.14)
  - Academic Policy Committee, 1976-1977 (Box 84, Folder XVII.15)
  - Admission and Financial Aid (CAFA), 1976-1977 (Box 84, Folder XVII.16)
  - ACUP - Long Range Planning Subcommittee, 1976-1977 (Box 84, Folder XVII.17)
  - Center for Energy Studies, 1976-1977 (Box 84, Folder XVII.18)
  - Cognitive Sciences - Sloan, 1978 (Box 84, Folder XVII.19)
  - Institutional Planning, 1976-1977 (Box 85, Folder XVII.20)
  - Committee on the status of Women, 1976-1977 (Box 85, Folder XVII.21)
  - Third World Coalition, 1976-1977 (Box 85, Folder XVII.22)
  - University Library, 1976-1977 (Box 85, Folder XVII.23)
- Internal Committees, 1977-1978; Series 18
  - Administrative Committee on Appointments & Promotions (ACAP), 1977-1978 (Box 86, Folder XVIII.1)
  - A & E, 1977-1978 (Box 86, Folder XVIII.2)
  - Admissions & Financial Aid, 1978 (Box 86, Folder XVIII.3)
  - Administrative Committee, 1977-1978 (Box 86, Folder XVIII.4)
  - Administrative Committee for Academic Development (ACAD), 1977-1978 (Box 86, Folder XVIII.5)
  - Academic Council, 1977-1978 (Box 86, Folder XVIII.6)
  - Investment Committee, 1977-1978 (Box 86, Folder XVIII.7)
  - Masters of Social Thought, 1977-1978 (Box 87, Folder XVIII.8)
  - Merton P. Stoltz, 1978 (Box 87, Folder XVIII.9)
  - Merton P. Stoltz, 1977 (Box 87, Folder XVIII.10)
  - Faculty Meeting, 1977-1978 (Box 87, Folder XVIII.11)
  - I.P.G. Meeting, 1977 (Box 87, Folder XVIII.12)
  - Administrative Council on Education, 1977-1978 (Box 87, Folder XVIII.13)
  - Greater Providence Chamber of Commerce Industry Retention Task Force, 1978 (Box 87, Folder XVIII.14)
  - Health Planning Council, 1977-1978 (Box 87, Folder XVIII.15)
  - RIHSEC - Rhode Island Health Sciences Education Council, 1977-1978 (Box 87, Folder XVIII.16)
  - SEARCH - RI Health Services Research, Inc., 1977-1978 (Box 88, Folder XVIII.17)
  - NEBHE (New England Board of Higher Education), 1977-1978 (Box 88, Folder XVIII.18)
  - Old Stone Bank - Audit Committee, 1977-1978 (Box 88, Folder XVIII.19)
  - Old Stone Bank -Management Committee, 1977-1978 (Box 88, Folder XVIII.20)
  - Old Stone Bank -PSA Committee, 1977-1978 (Box 88, Folder XVIII.21)
  - Old Stone Bank - Board of Directors, 1977-1978 (Box 88, Folder XVIII.22)
- Grants, 1964-1977; Series 19
  - Higher Education Act of 1965, 1965-1971 (Box 89, Folder XIX.1)
  - Higher Education Facilities Act of 1963, 1970-1971 (Box 89, Folder XIX.2)
  - Higher Education Facilities Act of 1963, 1964-1969 (Box 89, Folder XIX.3)
  - Higher Education Facilities Act of 1963(Bulletins), 1965-1971 (Box 89, Folder XIX.4)
  - Title I Application Worksheets, 1965 (Box 89, Folder XIX.5)
  - Title II HEFA Regulations and Instructions, 1965-1977 (Box 89, Folder XIX.6)
  - Title HEFA Jacobs Library, 1971-1972 (Box 89, Folder XIX.7)
  - Title I HEA Urban Observatory, 1970 (Box 89, Folder XIX.8)
  - Title I HEFA Geo-Math Complex, 1969 (Box 89, Folder XIX.9)
  - Title I HEFA Art Building, 1968 (Box 89, Folder XIX.10)
  - Title I HEFA Art Building, 1966 (Box 90, Folder XIX.11)
  - Title I HEFA Comprehensive Planning, 1967 (Box 90, Folder XIX.12)
  - Title I HEFA Science Library, 1965-1966 (Box 90, Folder XIX.13)
  - Title I Science Library -- Final Submission, 1966 (Box 90, Folder XIX.14)
  - Title I And II HEFA Science Library, 1968 (Box 90, Folder XIX.15)
  - Title I And III HEFA Regulations and Instructions, 1971 (Box 90, Folder XIX.16)
  - Title II Science Complex, 1968 (Box 90, Folder XIX.17)
  - Title II HEFA Geo- Math Complex, 1969 (Box 90, Folder XIX.18)
  - Title II HEA College Library Resources Program, 1970-1971 (Box 90, Folder XIX.19)
  - Title II HEA College Library Resources Program, 1969 (Box 90, Folder XIX.20)
  - Title II HEA College Library Resources Program, 1968 (Box 90, Folder XIX.21)
  - Title II HEA College Library Resources Program, 1967 (Box 91, Folder XIX.22)
  - Title II HEA Library Materials, 1966 (Box 91, Folder XIX.23)
  - Title II HEFA Science Library, 1965 (Box 91, Folder XIX.24)
  - Application for Grant for Construction of the Science Library, 1965 (Box 91, Folder XIX.25)
  - Application for Grant for Construction of the Science Library-- Copy, 1965 (Box 91, Folder XIX.26)
  - Title III HEFA Construction of Academic Facilities, 1966 (Box 91, Folder XIX.27)
  - Title IV HUD Pebroke Dorms, 1971-1972 (Box 91, Folder XIX.28)
  - Title IV HUD Pebroke Dorms, 1971-1972 (Box 91, Folder XIX.29)
  - Title IV HUD Pembroke Dormitories, 1970 (Box 91, Folder XIX.30)
  - Title IV HUD Pembroke Dormitories, 1969 (Box 91, Folder XIX.31)
  - Title V HEA Prospective Teacher Fellowships, 1966-1967 (Box 92, Folder XIX.32)
  - Title VI HEA Equipment and Materials - Physical Sciences and Arts, 1971-1972 (Box 92, Folder XIX.33)
  - Title VI HEA Equipment and Materials - Physical Sciences and Arts, 1970-1971 (Box 92, Folder XIX.34)
  - Title VI HEA Equipment and Materials - Physical Sciences and Arts, 1968-1969 (Box 92, Folder XIX.35)
  - Title VI HEA Equipment and Materials - Physical Sciences and Arts, 1967-1968 (Box 92, Folder XIX.36)
  - Title VI HEA Language Laboratory, 1966-1967 (Box 92, Folder XIX.37)
  - Title VI HEA Equipment and Materials, 1966 (Box 92, Folder XIX.38)
  - Title VI Undergraduate Teaching Equipment, 1966-1975 (Box 92, Folder XIX.39)
  - Title VI NSF Equipment Programs, 1974 (Box 92, Folder XIX.40)
  - Medical Library Assistance Act Sciences Library ( Medical Library), 1967-1968 (Box 93, Folder XIX.41)
  - Medical Library Assistance Act Sciences Library (Medical Library), 1966 (Box 93, Folder XIX.42)
  - Proposal to National Institutes of Health Under Medical Library Assistance Act, 1967 (Box 93, Folder XIX.43)
  - Proposal to National Institutes of Health Under Medical Library Assistance Act, 1967 (Box 93, Folder XIX.44)
  - HHFA Plans Graduate Center, 1964-1967 (Box 93, Folder XIX.45)
  - HHFA Loan Agreement Graduate Center, 1965-1966 (Box 93, Folder XIX.46)